

Krešimir Marić -Web Developer

kresimir@outlook.ie
www.kresomaric.com
+353/83/851-5011

Overview

Relocating to Dublin four years ago gave me potential to grow and learn outside of my starting career as a professional chef. My curiosity over time switched towards learning how to program since that was something I always wanted to do. Online courses gave me direction and end goal. Currently involved in online Front-End Web Developer diploma program at OpenClassrooms. It gave me opportunity to work on real life projects, collaborating with other students and presenting myself to mentors and project validators. Last two projects are focusing on React framework and also on JSON, AJAX, API integration. I am hard working person and eager to learn.

Professional Experience

Chef de partie

Doyle Collection/The Westbury, Dublin, Ireland

- Managing team of chefs and planning daily progress
- · Improving my attention to details
- · Maintaining hotel standards
- · Closely working with head-chef and restaurant manager

Chef

Keoghs cafe, Dublin, Ireland

- · Managing delivery and organising workspace
- · Setting up kitchen for daily operation
- · Communicating on intercom and passing orders

Chef/Pizza Chef

Konoba Babici, Umag, Croatia

- · Developing menu and sourcing ingredients
- · Teaching new staff
- · Planing orders and keeping inventory

Sep, 2015 - Jul, 2018

Mar, 2015 - Sep, 2015

Apr, 2009 - Nov, 2014

Technologies

During my study with OpenClassrooms I got to work with HTML5, CSS3, jQuery, JavaScript, Bootstrap, UML, MySql, Git, writing technical documentations and project briefs. In the future I would love to learn another programming language and explore different technologies.

Education

Bachelor's-level EQF 6 "Web developer (Développeur(euse) d'application)" = "OpenClassrooms" = Dublin, Ireland = 2019

Leaving Certificate – Culinary Arts • "Antun Horvat" Trade school • Djakovo, Croatia • 2005

Certifications

Learn to code with JavaScript (OpenClassrooms) - Feb 2019

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/2516492393

Build your website with HTML5 and CSS3 (OpenClassrooms) - Nov 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/5487923867

Build quick and beautiful WordPress sites (OpenClassrooms) - Oct 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/9590507750

Understanding the Web (OpenClassrooms) - Oct 2018

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/2947433099

Think like a computer: Understanding the logic of programming (OpenClassrooms) - May 2019

Credential url: https://openclassrooms.com/en/course-certificates/3877891772